hardrockhotel.com 2018-10-27

# Privacy Policy • Terms of Use • Mobile Program • About • Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas

### **PRIVACY POLICY**

#### Effective Date: November 13, 2015

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas, owned by HRHH Hotel/Casino, LLC ("We" or "HRHH") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This privacy policy (together with our terms of use Terms of Use and any other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any information (which may include personal data) we collect from you, or that you provide to us, through this website will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.

By visiting [www.HARDROCKHOTEL.com](http://www.hardrockhotel.com/) (the "Site") you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy (including as updated or amended from time to time). If, for any reason, you do not agree to the terms of this policy, please stop using the Site immediately.

#### WHO WE ARE

As used in this Privacy Policy, "HRHH" includes HRHH Hotel/Casino, LLC, BREF HR, LLC and their subsidiaries.

#### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

When you use the Site or contact us by e-mail, social media, online feedback forms, or at the Resort, we may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information you give us, including:

    * Forms filled out by you on the Site or at the Resort, including booking accommodations, requests for proposal for conferences or special events, requests to be included in email alerts, text message alerts, or other inquiries;

    * Content of electric correspondence with us;

    * Site registration and use of your account and features such as the Backstage Pass Rewards Club, including your use of the Backstage Pass at the Resorts;

    * Participation in media functions on the Site;

    * Entering a competition, promotion or survey;

    * Reporting a problem or requesting support for the Site or your stay with us.

The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, payment information, comments, or any other information you provide to us.

  * Information we collect about you.

With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:

    * Technical information, including IP address, login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;

    * Information about your visit, including the full URL clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time);

    * Pages you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

  * Information we receive from other sources.

    * We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites operated by HRHH or the other services HRHH provides. In addition, if you use a third party service to book a room we will receive your booking information from that third party. This data may be shared internally and combined with data collected on this site or at the Resorts. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers) and may receive information about you from them.

#### HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * Information you give to us. We will use this information:

    * To help us respond to your queries;

    * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;

    * To facilitate your stay or visit with us at the Resorts, including services and benefits related to the Backstage Pass Rewards Club, shows or events you may attend, and gaming or other entertainment at the Resort;

    * To provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about. Where required by applicable law, we will seek your prior written consent before doing so;

    * To provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the order form or registration form);

    * To notify you about changes to our service;

    * To manage your access to the services;

    * To allow you to interact with our Site;

    * To allow you to share information from our Site on third party social media platforms;

    * To comply with legal and regulatory requirements;

  * Information we collect about you. We will use this information:

    * To administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;

    * To improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

    * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;

    * As part of our efforts to keep our site and the Resort safe and secure;

    * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;

    * To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them, if we have received your consent to do so;

    * To provide or permit third parties to provide targeted advertising via websites you visit about goods or services that you may find interesting (see more on this in our Cookies policy).

  * Information we receive from other sources.

    * We may combine information from other sources with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may use this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive);

    * If you sign up to give us access to your social media pages you are consenting to us receiving information collected about you via that social media platform (we will only collect the data you give your consent for us to collect when you sign up for this option).

#### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies and with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you, including fulfilling reservations and offering certain products and services in connection with our Site and the Resort.

  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our Site.

#### We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

  * If HRHH or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of HRHH, our customers, the Resort, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

#### STORAGE AND SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers or secure services controlled by third parties on our behalf. Any payment transactions through the Site will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.

#### COOKIES

Our website may use cookies or other tracking technologies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

#### Children

The Site is not directed toward children under 13 years of age nor does HRHH knowingly collect information from children under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to submit any personally identifiable information to HRHH.

#### YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) or text communications, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you or telephone number to send the text communications to you, as applicable. You may opt out of certain communications such as customer feedback or marketing emails or postal mail through the instructions in the email or text, as applicable, or by clicking here or by contacting us as described in the "Contact Us" section below.

Some Browsers support a “Do Not Track” feature, which is intended to be a signal to websites that you do not wish to be tracked across different websites you visit. Certain legal obligations require that we disclose how websites we operate, such as our registration page, react to Do Not Track signals.

Where provided under applicable law, you may have the right to ask us for a list of your personal data we share with third parties and information regarding those third parties, if the third parties use the personal data for their direct marketing purposes. You can exercise this right at any time by contacting us as described in the "Contact Us" section below.

#### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any material changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page prior to the change becoming effective and notify you through the Site or, where appropriate, by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy. These changes will become effective upon obtaining your consent, if necessary, as required under local law. If you do not agree or consent to these updates or changes, do not continue to use the Site.

#### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the address as provided below in the "Contact Us" section. In your request, please specify that you want a "California Privacy Rights Notice". Please allow 30 days for a response.

#### CONTACT US

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [contactus@hrhvegas.com](mailto:contactus@hrhvegas.com)

#### OR

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas  
4455 Paradise Road  
Las Vegas, NV 89169

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by calling us at [(702) 693-5000](tel:7026935000). If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at [(702) 693-5000](tel:7026935000).

Upon request we provide Site visitors with access to all information including proprietary information that we maintain about them. Customers can access this information and if errors are found, request that this information be corrected by calling us at [(702) 693-5000](tel:7026935000).

* * *

### **Terms of Use**

#### WELCOME TO THE INTERNET SITE OF THE HARD ROCK & CASINO

Please read these terms of use carefully before using this Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site. By using this site, you signify your agreement to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, you may not use the Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of these terms of use at any time in accordance with the procedures set forth below in the paragraph labeled "Amendment."

#### RESTRICTIONS ON USE OF MATERIALS

All materials contained in any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site are the copyrighted property of Hard Rock Hotel & Casino, or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies and/or third-party licensors. All trademarks, service marks, trade names, and trade dress are proprietary to Hard Rock Hotel & Casino, Inc., or its affiliates or licensees. No material from any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site or any Internet site owned, operated, licensed, or controlled by us may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, except that you may download one copy of the materials on any single computer for your personal, noncommercial home use only, provided that (i) you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices, (ii) you make no modifications to the materials, (iii) you do not use the materials in a manner that suggests an association with any of our products, services, or brands, and (iv) you do not download quantities of materials to a database that can be used to avoid future downloads from any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site. The use of any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino material on any other Web site or computer environment is prohibited. In the event you download software from any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site, the software, including any files, images incorporated in or generated by the software, and data accompanying the software (collectively, the "Software") are licensed to you by us or third-party licensors for your personal, noncommercial home use only. We do not transfer title to the Software to you. You own the medium on which the Software is recorded, but we (or our third-party licensors) retain full and complete title to the Software and all intellectual property rights therein. You may not redistribute, sell, auction, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reduce the Software to a human-readable form.

#### SUBMISSIONS

We are pleased to hear from our visitors and welcome your comments regarding our products and services. Unfortunately, however, our long-standing company policy does not allow us to accept or consider creative ideas, suggestions, or materials other than those that we have specifically requested. We hope you will understand that it is the intent of this policy to avoid the possibility of future misunderstandings when projects developed by our professional staff might seem to others to be similar to their own creative work. Please do not send us any unsolicited original creative materials such as stories or ideas, screenplays, or original artwork. While we do value your feedback on our services and products, we request that you be specific in your comments on those services and products, and not submit any creative ideas, suggestions, or materials (unless specifically requested by us). If, through participation in certain activities, you send any material (e.g., postings to chat, boards, or contests) or, despite our request, you send us unsolicited creative suggestions, ideas, notes, drawings, concepts, or other information (collectively, the "Submissions"), the Submissions shall be deemed, and shall remain, our property. None of the Submissions shall be subject to any obligation of confidentiality on our part and we shall not be liable for any use or disclosure of any Submissions. Without limitation of the foregoing, we shall exclusively own all now-known or hereafter existing rights to the Submissions of every kind and nature throughout the universe and shall be entitled to unrestricted use of the Submissions for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, without compensation to the provider of the Submissions or any other person or entity.

#### FORUMS AND PUBLIC COMMUNICATION

"Forum" means a chat area, message board, instant messaging, mobile messaging or e-mail function (including, but not limited to, electronic greeting cards) offered as part of any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site. If you participate in any Forum within a Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site, you agree to follow our terms set forth below. You acknowledge that anything you submit to a Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site by way of any Forum is routed through Hard Rock Hotel & Casino’s servers and the Internet and that, therefore, you have no expectation of privacy with regard to any such submission. You acknowledge that the Forums and features on Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Sites are forums for public and not private communications. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, for example, via message boards or chat, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online; you make such disclosures at your own risk. Users or visitors shall remain solely responsible for the content of their messages in the Forums. We are not responsible for the content or opinions posted or sent by users in any Forum. You take responsibility for postings under your username and use the information provided in the Forums at your own risk. We reserve the right to remove or edit content from any Forum at any time and for any reason although we have no duty to do so. When participating in a Forum, never assume that people are who they say they are, know what they say they know, or are affiliated with whom they say they are affiliated with in any chat room, message board, or other user-generated content area. Information obtained in a Forum may not be reliable, and it is not a good idea to take any action, including to trade or make any investment decisions, based solely or largely on information you cannot confirm. We cannot be responsible for the content or accuracy of any information, and shall not be responsible for any trading, investment, or any other decisions made based on such information.

#### HOUSE RULES

The following is a list of the House Rules of conduct for the Hard Rock Hotel & Casino sites. By using the Hard Rock Hotel & Casino sites you agree not to do any of the following:

  1. Post, distribute, or otherwise make available or transmit any data, text, message, or computer file that we deem to be: (a) defamatory, abusive, harassing, insulting, threatening, or that could be deemed to be stalking;

(b) bigoted, hateful, or racially offensive; (c) vulgar, obscene, or sexually explicit (language or images); or that (d) encourages or advocates illegal activity or the discussion of illegal activities with the intent to commit them;

  2. Post, distribute, or otherwise make available or transmit any data, text, message, computer file, or other material that infringes and/or violates any right of a third party or any domestic or international law, rule, or regulation, including but not limited to: (a) copyright, patent, trademark, or other proprietary rights; (b) right of privacy (specifically, you must not distribute another person’s personal information of any kind without their express permission) or publicity; (c) any confidentiality obligation;

  3. Advertise or sell any products, services or otherwise (whether or not for profit), or solicit others or use any Forum for commercial purposes of any kind,

  4. Post, distribute, or otherwise make available or transmit any software or other computer files that contain a virus or other harmful component;

  5. Impersonate any person or entity or misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person or entity;

  6. Engage in antisocial, disruptive, or destructive acts, including "flaming," "spamming," "flooding," "trolling," and "griefing" as those terms are commonly understood and used on the Internet;

  7. Delete any legal notices, disclaimers, or proprietary notices such as copyright or trademark symbols, or modify any logos that you do not own or have express permission to modify;

  8. Post, distribute, or otherwise make available or transmit material or make statements that do not generally pertain to the designated topic or theme of any Forum.

Additionally, you may use electronic greeting cards or mobile messaging for noncommercial purposes only. You must furnish your actual e-mail address or mobile phone number in order to send a card or message. Any business use, "remailing," or other high-volume application is strictly prohibited. You are not permitted to send cards or messages using an automated program. Electronic greeting cards and mobile messages may not contain inappropriate language or images or copyrighted material (without the consent of the copyright holder) or encourage illegal activity. Electronic greeting cards and mobile messages that violate these guidelines will not be delivered. We reserve the right to remove any material, and if we deem appropriate, to turn over to law enforcement officials, any material, including message, e-mail, or posting, that is in violation of these House Rules. We also reserve the right to remove messages, e-mails, or postings that do not pertain to the designated topic or theme of the Forum. We also reserve the right to comply with any order or otherwise cooperate with law enforcement officials regarding the identification of any user alleged to be using a Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site in violation of the law.

#### CONTENT LINKED TO ANY HARD ROCK & CASINO SITE

You should be aware that when you are on a Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Hard Rock Hotel & Casino pages that take you outside of our service. We make no representations concerning the content of sites listed in any of our directories. Consequently, we cannot be held responsible for the accuracy, relevancy, copyright compliance, legality, or decency of material contained in sites listed in our search results or otherwise linked to a Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site.

#### DISCLAIMER

The materials in the Hard Rock Hotel & Casino sites are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind, either express or implied. To the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, we disclaim all warranties, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and noninfringement. We do not warrant that the functions contained in the materials on any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site or the servers that make such materials available are free of viruses or other harmful components. We do not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials on any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair, or correction. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusion may not apply to you.

We explicitly disclaim any responsibility for the accuracy, content, or availability of information found on sites that link to or from any Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Site. We cannot ensure that you will be satisfied with any products or services that you purchase from a third-party site that links to or from any Hard Rock Hotel Casino and Hotel Site or third-party content on our sites. We do not endorse any of the merchandise, nor have we taken any steps to confirm the accuracy or reliability of, any of the information contained in such third-party sites or content. We do not make any representations or warranties as to the security of any information (including, without limitation, credit card and other personal information) you might be requested to give any third party, and you hereby irrevocably waive any claim against us with respect to such sites and third-party content. We strongly encourage you to make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online or offline transaction with any of these third parties.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

We will ask you to voluntarily supply us with personally identifiable information (such as your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number or credit card number) to provide you with a particular service you request, (including when you make a reservation, sign up for e-mail alerts, use the "contact us" page, e-mail us, establish a Web user profile, and at other times), For example, if you would like to make a reservation at one of our hotels, we will ask you for information such as name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number. We will also use your email address to send a confirmation and, if necessary, we might also use other information to contact you for help in processing the reservation. We will also use your email address to notify you about special offers and promotions as described in the email section of this privacy statement

#### MOBILE PROGRAM

#### Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas Terms & Conditions

Service Description: Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas is offering a SMS text alert program. Upon joining, you will receive a confirmation text to confirm your participation in this program. Once enrolled, you will receive text messages with the latest Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas news, updates, promotions and exclusive mobile offers. To join, just text HROCK to 97580. By texting HROCK to 97580, you agree to receive 5 autodialed marketing messages per month from Hard Rock to your number. Consent is not required to make a purchase. Message and data rates may apply. Text STOP to 97580 to cancel at any time. Text HELP to 97580 for help.

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas can also use your mobile phone’s location to send you the latest Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas news, updates, promotions and exclusive mobile offers based on your location. To join the location program, just text LOCATION to 97580. By texting LOCATION to 97580, you agree to receive 5 autodialed marketing messages per month from Hard Rock to your number. Consent is not required to make a purchase. Message and data rates may apply. Text STOP to 97580 to cancel at any time. Text HELP to 97580 for help.

Terms & Conditions: Mobile phone user privacy is extremely important to us at Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas. Location coordinates are only gathered after the mobile phone user has agreed to use this service. The agreement process is commenced by a user texting LOCATION to 97580. An Opt-In SMS text message to the user’s Mobile Phone is then triggered. The user can then accept this agreement by replying YES MM/DD/YYYY (birthdate) to the Opt-In SMS text message. At any time the user can cancel Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas Location Service’s ability to obtain their location coordinates by texting STOP to 97580 or replying STOP to any message.

Limitations – Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas’ General SMS Service is available only on Boost, AT&T, T-Mobile®, Dobson, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, U.S. Cellular, C Spire Wireless, Virgin Mobile, Cellcom, NTelos, GetLisa, & Cricket Communications. Other Network Carriers will be added as they become available. You must be 21 years of age or older to use this service.

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas’ Location Service is available only on Boost, AT&T, T-Mobile®, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, U.S. Cellular & Virgin Mobile. The location service will not be available if the phone is roaming or is turned off. Other Network Carriers will be added as they become available. You must be 21 years of age or older to use this service.

Location coordinates (longitude, latitude, and radius) will be obtained only when we have proper authorization from the user.

Message and Data rates may apply. Messages will be sent 5 times per month. For location service messages, receiving alerts is based on your profile and proximity to Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas.

General SMS Program Opt-In/Opt-Out: To sign-up text HROCK to 97580. To cancel: Text STOP to 97580. For Support text HELP to 97580 or call [855-880-8878](tel:18558808878) or email: [smshelp@hrhvegas.com](mailto:smshelp@hrhvegas.com)

Location SMS Program Opt-In/Opt-Out: To sign-up text LOCATION to 97580. To cancel: Text STOP to 97580. For Support text HELP to 97580 or call [855-880-8878](tel:18558808878) or email: [smshelp@hrhvegas.com](mailto:smshelp@hrhvegas.com)

* * *

### **Mobile Program**

Receive Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas alerts on your mobile phone containing special offers, event and ticketing info.

It’s easy to join; text HROCK to 97580. By texting HROCK to 97580, you agree to receive 5 autodialed marketing messages per month from Hard Rock to your number. Consent is not required to make a purchase. Message and data rates may apply. Text STOP to 97580 to cancel at any time. Text HELP to 97580 for help.

There is no cost to join. You can also email our support team at [smshelp@hrhvegas.com.](mailto:smshelp@hrhvegas.com)

This program is available to subscribers of Boost, AT&T, T-Mobile®, Dobson, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, Metro PCS, U.S. Cellular, C Spire Wireless, Virgin Mobile, Cellcom, NTelos, GetLisa, & Cricket Communications. You must be 18 years of age or older to use this service. You also agree to Terms of Use.

#### Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas Location-Based Alerts

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas can use your mobile phone’s locational information to send you Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas news, updates, promotions and exclusive mobile offers based on your location, but only if you want us to!

The Location program is available to subscribers of Boost, AT&T, T-Mobile®, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, U.S. Cellular, Virgin Mobile & Cricket Communications. You must be 21 years of age or older to use this service. You also agree to Terms of Use

By opting into this program on short code 97580 you will be sharing your phone's location with Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas. Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas may use this information to send you Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas news, updates, promotions and exclusive mobile offers based on your location!

To share your phone's location please text LOCATION to 97580. By texting LOCATION to 97580, you agree to receive 5 autodialed marketing messages per month from Hard Rock to your number. Consent is not required to make a purchase. Message and data rates may apply. Text STOP to 97580 to cancel at any time. Text HELP to 97580 for help.

We respect your privacy. Our privacy policy can be found here: Privacy Policy

This short code program is managed by Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas. [www.hardrockhotel.com](http://www.hardrockhotel.com/)

#### Contact Info:

Hard Rock Hotel & Casino Las Vegas  
4455 Paradise Road  
Las Vegas, NV 89169
